Contact

stephenmary@ymail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mary-williams-28906934 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Acute Care

BLS

Nursing

Certifications

CNOR

Certified Surgical Services Educator

Mary Williams

RN, BSN, CNOR

United States

Summary

16 years of nursing experience in perioperative nursing setting and critical care area. Certified operating room nurse with a certificate in perioperative nurse education. Implementation of startup education programs transitioning nursing professionals level of expertise from novice to proficient through AORN Periop 101 program training material and online training in conjunction with hands on experience. Designed surgical prep simulation model. Clinical case review nurse experience, working with contractors as an expert in the field of nursing.

Experience

The University of Texas Medical Branch Circulating Nurse March 2020 - Present (5 months)

Houston Methodist 3 years 3 months

Registered Nurse February 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 2 months) United States

Clinical Coordinator OR January 2017 - March 2020 (3 years 3 months) United States

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center 3 years 8 months

OR Clinical Educator
June 2014 - January 2017 (2 years 8 months)

Perioperative RN June 2013 - June 2014 (1 year 1 month) Webster, TX Memorial Hermann Health System perioperative RN October 2011 - May 2013 (1 year 8 months)

Good Samaritan Hospital

RN

January 2011 - October 2011 (10 months)

Puyallup, Washington

Travel RN

OR Nurse

August 2008 - October 2011 (3 years 3 months)

King's Daughters Medical Center RN CVICU

June 2006 - July 2008 (2 years 2 months)

Ashland, Kentucky

Open heart recovery

Cabell Huntington Hospital

RN

June 2004 - July 2006 (2 years 2 months)

Education

Grand Canyon University

BSN, Nursing Practice · (2019)

Ohio University

Applied science, Nursing · (2016)

ACC

ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2003 - 2004)

Ohio University

Nursing · (2002 - 2003)

Shawnee State University

Nursing · (2000 - 2002)